chisms.net 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | CHISMS.net

This privacy policy sets out how “Chisms.net” uses and protects any information that you give “Chisms.net” when you use this website.

“Chisms.net” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

“Chisms.net” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from August 8, 2015.

Privacy Principles

We value your privacy as much as we value ours. That’s why we at Chisms.net wish to emphasize these underlying principles:

– We make it a point not to ask for personal information that is irrelevant to the operation of the site.

– We won’t disclose your personal information to anybody, unless it’s for legal purposes, company and/or product development or to safeguard the rights of the company.

E-mail, Feedback and Forum Facilities  
If at any time this Website offers any e-mail, feedback or forum facilities, we may collect the information, which you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Keeping our records accurate  
We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.

Security of your personal data  
We have implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate.

How we use cookies  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Policy changes  
Changes in this policy will be posted on our Websites. You are advised to check our Websites regularly to view our most recent privacy policy.
